<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://lidesdk.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lidesdk.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>lide shell release 0.1.13 &#34;security patch&#34;</title>
      <link>https://lidesdk.github.io/post/shell-release-0.1.13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lidesdk.github.io/post/shell-release-0.1.13/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s called first security patch because on this version all updates are related to security. Update is required because numerous fixes are done.
A new version of inifile was written using lide framework.
0.1.13 - Add luacurl to runtime. - Security patches. - lide.http 0.2.1. - Change inifile for inifile 0.1 (lide based). - Added repos-api. - Fix: Update lide interpreter for Linux
Required OS: Windows XP to Windows 10 Release date: 10/13/2018 Release version: 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lide shell release 0.1.12 &#34;first patch&#34;</title>
      <link>https://lidesdk.github.io/post/shell-release-0.1.12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lidesdk.github.io/post/shell-release-0.1.12/</guid>
      <description>This version is called the first patch because on this version numerous bugs are fixed and we apply corrections to the code, the first patch of 0.1 version is the most important patch because has security features and updates about github api and repository databases structure. With this version you can do specific version installs, update modules and execute lide in arm architectures (aarch64). Many changes are added and fixed bugs, changes here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lide shell release 0.1</title>
      <link>https://lidesdk.github.io/post/shell-release-0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lidesdk.github.io/post/shell-release-0.1/</guid>
      <description>Lide Shell is a project that gives us the possibility to interact with a totally controlled environment for the execution of the Lide framework. It is built with different libraries that are interoperable with most Lua interpreters that are used by default.
In addition, the Lua scripts allow us to manage different libraries or modules that are organized in &amp;ldquo;packages&amp;rdquo; according to a specific specification called lide.manifest.
You can install lide shell on Windows OS using automatic installer:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>